<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tweakflow: embeddable scripting language for the JVM on tweakflow - safe embeddable scripting language for the JVM</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tweakflow: embeddable scripting language for the JVM on tweakflow - safe embeddable scripting language for the JVM</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Embedding Guide</title>
      <link>/embedding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/embedding.html</guid>
      <description>Requirements Tweakflow requires Java 8 or later. Builds are tested against JDK 8 and JDK 11.
Getting tweakflow You can get the tweakflow jar from the releases page or from maven central:
&amp;lt;dependency&amp;gt; &amp;lt;groupId&amp;gt;com.twineworks&amp;lt;/groupId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;artifactId&amp;gt;tweakflow&amp;lt;/artifactId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;0.14.0&amp;lt;/version&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dependency&amp;gt;  Tweakflow values Whenever the application is exchanging data with tweakflow code, it does so through immutable value objects of class Value. Variable values, function parameters, function return values, everything is a value in tweakflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>/getting-started.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started.html</guid>
      <description>Getting started This document is an interactive step-by-step guide to tweakflow expressions. Its goal is to give you a feeling for the syntax and expressive capabilities of tweakflow.
Requirements Tweakflow requires Java 8 or later. Builds are tested against JDK 8 and JDK 11.
Getting tweakflow Download the latest release jar. You can also obtain it from maven central using the following dependency:
&amp;lt;dependency&amp;gt; &amp;lt;groupId&amp;gt;com.twineworks&amp;lt;/groupId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;artifactId&amp;gt;tweakflow&amp;lt;/artifactId&amp;gt; &amp;lt;version&amp;gt;0.14.0&amp;lt;/version&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dependency&amp;gt;  Starting a REPL Launch the interactive REPL using:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal notice</title>
      <link>/legal_notice.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal_notice.html</guid>
      <description>Legal Notice This website&amp;rsquo;s content is managed by Twineworks GmbH
Helmholtzstr. 28
10587 Berlin
Germany
email: hi@twineworks.com
phone: +49 30 398 879 22
Represented by Slawomir Chodnicki
Registry Amtsgericht Berlin-Charlottenburg
HRB: 155466 B
International VAT ID No. as specified in ยง 27a of the German VAT Law DE293085796
Person responsible for content in accordance with ยง 55 Abs. 2 RStV Twineworks GmbH
Slawomir Chodnicki
Helmholtzstr. 28
10587 Berlin
Germany</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>/support.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support.html</guid>
      <description>Support Tweakflow is using the business friendly MIT open source license. However, open source does not mean you&amp;rsquo;re on your own. Tweakflow is developed by Twineworks GmbH. Twineworks offers commercial support, training, and consulting services for tweakflow projects. Get in touch if you&amp;rsquo;d like us to support a project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The tweakflow language</title>
      <link>/reference.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reference.html</guid>
      <description>Motivation Tweakflow offers a way for JVM applications to evaluate user-supplied expressions in a formula-like notation. Tweakflow supports user-defined functions, libraries, and modules, to support applications in which the user-supplied computations can grow to non-trivial size and complexity. The host application is in control of how much sophistication is available to users.
Requirements Tweakflow runs on the JVM. Java 8 or later is required. Builds are tested against JDK 8 and JDK 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>/tools.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools.html</guid>
      <description>Language Tools The tweakflow jar offers entry points for some language tools that can be executed standalone. An interactive REPL, a runner that evaluates all given modules and calls a main function, and a documentation tool that extracts doc and metadata from modules.
Interactive REPL To launch the REPL run:
$ java -jar tweakflow-0.14.0.jar repl  The acronym repl stands for &amp;lsquo;read evaluate process loop&amp;rsquo;. You should see a prompt similar to this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>std.tf</title>
      <link>/modules/std.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modules/std.html</guid>
      <description>module std.tf The standard module contains basic functions for general computing tasks.
All samples run in the interactive tweakflow REPL which you can launch using:
java -jar tweakflow-0.14.0.jar repl   library core The core library contains utility functions to process values at a basic level.
 id (any x) -&amp;gt; any
Identity function. Returns x.
&amp;gt; core.id(&amp;quot;foo&amp;quot;) &amp;quot;foo&amp;quot; &amp;gt; core.id({:a &amp;quot;b&amp;quot;}) { :a &amp;quot;b&amp;quot; } &amp;gt; core.id(nil) nil   inspect (x) -&amp;gt; string</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>